# Taha Hussien Abdelhameed Hassan

# Web Developer

Address: Nasr City, Cairo, Egypt Phone: +201150651396 Email: ryhanytaha@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

More two years of experience in developing websites in different web programming languages, I received a 6-months internship in a software company, then a one-month intensive training at the National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) in web development using Node Js and Angular.

looking for a web developer job, to gain more in depth skills and experience, to work in large websites, various tools and frameworks.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

1/2021 – present

# Front End Web Developer, Perfect Work Group Company, Giza

- Worked for a company as a web developer.
- Convert XD files to HTML, CSS, JS.
- Use Vue Js and React Js frameworks.

11/2018 - 12/2020

## Web Developer, Advertizer Company, Nasr city

- Worked for a company as a web developer.
- Developing various landing pages, websites and single page applications from scratch.

04/2019 - present

# Web Developer, freelancer

worked in many freelance projects with many clients for example:

- a cars website: http://golden-rents.com/
- moving furniture landing page: http://el3saly-trans.com/
- Advensco (software company): https://www.advensco.com/

**EDUCATION** 2014 – 2018

Bachelor's degree in science, Faculty of science, Al Azhar University.

Certified as a Web Developer, Node Js and Angular Certification, National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

## **SKILLS**

#### **Technical**:

- HTML5 Pug
- CSS3 SASS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Java Script ECMA Script Type Script
- Vue Js
- React JS
- Node JS
- WordPress
- Photoshop

# language:

English:

good in listening, good in Writing, very good in reading and good in speaking

• Arabic: native lang.

## PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Communication skills:

Gained through my experience as a web developer work with many freelance clients.

• Problem solving:

Lots of problems happen while writing code, gained experiences in solving these problems.

• Time management:

Through my work and following the various courses and self-development, I was able to develop this skill.

• Teamwork:

I have acquired this skill on a graduate project and through working on various projects with other people.

# PERSONAL INFORMAION

Date of birth: 01/01/1997Nationality: Egyption

• Marital status: Single

• Military service: Exemption

#### Links

• LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/taharehany

• GitHub: https://github.com/taharehany

• Facebook: www.facebook.com/taha.rehany

• Website: www.rehany.site

#### REFERENCES

References and Certificates are upon under request.